const quiz2data = [
    {
      question: "Tim arrived at 9:35, but the train ___ already left.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "had", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "has", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the past perfect to show that something happened before another action in the past."
   },
    {
      question: "We ___ for about 5 hours in the desert when the police found us.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "had been walking", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "had walked", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the past perfect continuous to talk about how long something went on up to a particular past time."
   },
    {
      question: "I ___ this song many times before.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "had been hearing", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "had heard", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We use the past perfect to talk about how many times something happened in a period up to a particular past time."
   },
    {
      question: "The lights went off because my brother ___ the electricity bill.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "hadn't paid", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "didn't paid", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the past perfect to make it clear that one event happened before another in the past."
   },
    {
      question: "My clothes were wet because I ___ my car.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "had been washing", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "was washing", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the past perfect continuous to show that something started in the past and continued up until another time in the past. This is usually used to show a result at a time in the past."
   },
    {
      question: "I ___ to visit the National Gallery before I left London, but it's closed on Sundays.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "had wanted", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "wanted", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the past perfect when we say what we wanted or hoped to do, but didn't."
   },
    {
      question: "When we got to the spot, the fire ___ all night.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "had burnt", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "had been burning", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We use the past perfect continuous to show that something started in the past and continued up until another time in the past."
   },
    {
      question: "___ you visited Paris before this trip?",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "Had", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "Have", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the past perfect to make it clear that one event happened before another in the past."
   },
    {
      question: "At last the train came, I ___ been waiting for 15 minutes.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "had", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "have", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the past perfect continuous to show that something started in the past and continued up until another time in the past."
   },
    {
      question: "My graduation day was the best day I ___ ever had.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "had", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "have", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the past perfect when we are reporting our experience up to a point in the past."
   },
    {
      question: "The roads were blocked in the morning. It ___ all night.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "had been snowing", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "was snowing", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the past perfect continuous to show that something started in the past and continued up until another time in the past. We use this tense to emphasize the duration or length of that action (all night). The past continuous shows an action in progress at a specific moment in the past (at 3pm)."
   },
    {
      question: "Bob ____ for the test, so he was very nervous.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "hadn't studied", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "didn't study", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use the past perfect to make it clear that one event happened before another in the past."
   },
  ]
export default quiz2data
